// Quiz data
let questions = [
    { question: "Why was 6 afaid of 7?", options: ["Pineapple", "7, 8, 9", "He has a gun"], correct: 1 },
    { question: "What is the capital of Fortnite?", options: ["Loot Lake", "Tilted Towers", "Moisty mire"], correct: 1 },
    { question: "What color is the sky in a blood moon?", options: ["Black", "Brown", "Red"], correct: 0 },
    { question: "How many weeks in a day?", options: ["Kratos", "R-301", "1/7"], correct: 2 },
    { question: "What is 70 - 3?", options: ["69", "67", "41"], correct: 1 },
    { question: "Deal or no deal?", options: ["No deal!", "Seal!", "Deal!", "No seal!"], correct: 1 },
    { question: "How do you kill a werewolf?", options: ["Shoe Polish", "Black Pudding ", "Gravy Granules", "Cillit Bang"], correct: 0 },
    { question: "What flavor is cardboard", options: ["Honey", "Pork Scratchings", "Egg Mayonaise", "Talc"], correct: 2 },
    { question: "Whatdo you call a wingless fly?", options: ["A Flap", "A plum", "A Walk", "Jason"], correct: 2 },
    { question: "What is 5 Ã— 4?", options: ["15", "20", "25"], correct: 1 }
];

// Quiz start
score = 0;
currentQuestion = 0;

// Display  question  
function showQuestion() {
    let q = questions[currentQuestion];
    
}

// Check if answer is right
function checkAnswer() {
    
}

// Go to next question
function nextQuestion() {

}

// SHow score
function showScore() {
    
}

